Robin Hammargren Roos - Resume

email: robinhammargren09@gmail.com

phone: 0468753465

residence: Annerley/Brisbane

my portfolio: https://robinhammargren09.wixsite.com/ux-design-portfolio

About Me

My name is Robin and I am a 24-year-old man living in Brisbane. Since 2022 I have been in Australia where I have studied UX & Web Design.

People tell me I am confident, honest, and a social and outgoing person. I get motivated by helping others and am always striving to improve.

I am available Monday to Friday and willing to work weekends. I have experience in cleaning, customer service, and teamwork.

Career History

Venue Staff - Suncorp Stadium

Feb 2024 - Present

My responsibilities include changing bins, hosing seats, and blowing rubbish.

Team Member - Coles Supermarkets

Oct 2023 - Present

I work in produce where I clean, refill, and help customers find what they need.

Cleaner - Fujifilm Business Innovation

Jan 2023 - Aug 2023

At Fujifilm, I cleaned kitchens, offices, elevators, windows, and toilets.

Mailman - Postnord

Jan 2022 - Aug 2022

I sorted and collected mail before going to the neighborhoods where I delivered the mail.

Mover - Lindomeflyttningsbyrå

Mar 2021 - Dec 2021

As a team, we went out to businesses and private homes where we helped people remove their belongings from one house to another.

Skills

Cleaning

Teamwork

Social & Confident

Honest & Hardworking

Emotional Intelligence

Autonomy

Positive Attitude

Interests

Traveling

Exercising

Football

Swimming

Hiking

Reading

Languages

Swedish

English

Education

Diploma of UX & Web Design (1.5 Years)